(Leonard:)Okay, I got to...
I-I just...
I got to ask:
(Leonard:)what makes you think
that your relationship
(Leonard:)is so wonderful
and ours isn't?
(Sheldon:)For starters,
(Sheldon:)we enjoy spending time together.
(Leonard:)So do we.
(Leonard:)And I've seen you guys
ignore each other for hours
(Leonard:)doing totally
different things.
(Sheldon:)It's called parallel play.
(Leonard:)Yeah, toddlers
do that.
(Sheldon:)Not as well as we do.
(clicks tongue)
(Leonard:)You believe this guy? He has to
be the best at everything.
(Penny:)So what?
Why do you even care?
(Sheldon:)Oh, listen to them.
(Sheldon:)Not even married
and the honeymoon's over.
(Leonard:)Whatever. You can't
even go on a date
(Leonard:)without checking your
relationship agreement.
(Sheldon:)If you've got a problem basing
a relationship on a contract,
(Sheldon:)I'd like to tell you
about 13 plucky colonies
(Sheldon:)that entered
a "relationship agreement"
(Sheldon:)called the U.S. Constitution.
(Sheldon:)And it may not be cool
to say so,
(Sheldon:)but I think that love affair
is still pretty hot today.